thescooterstore.com 2012-12-25

# The SCOOTER Store – Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy 

##### Our Commitment to Privacy

Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with visitors to our site [www.thescooterstore.com](http://www.thescooterstore.com/) (the "Site"). This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how this Site collects, uses and safeguards the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site. **By visiting the Site or submitting your personal data, you accept the terms described in this Privacy Policy. From time to time we may modify this Privacy Policy**. If it becomes necessary to make changes to this Privacy Policy, such changes will be indicated on the Site. 

##### What Information Do We Collect and How Do We Use It?

When you visit this Site you may provide The SCOOTER Store with two types of information: (1) personal information you knowingly and actively choose to disclose to The SCOOTER Store that is collected on an individual basis ("Active Information"), and (2) Site user information collected, in a way not visible to you, on an aggregate basis as you and others browse this Site ("Passive Information").

##### Active Information You Choose to Disclose

When you submit information to our Site, such as by communicating with us through the Site, The SCOOTER Store may collect your name, mailing address, email address, phone number and other personal information that you may voluntarily provide when you use the Site. The SCOOTER Store uses Active Information to allow one of our representatives to contact you to further discuss your inquiries (which may include employment opportunities with The SCOOTER Store), to provide to you content that is relevant to your interests, and in the furtherance of other purposes for which you specifically provide the Active Information. Email addresses are collected to build "House Lists" for future marketing campaigns that you may opt out of at anytime. If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. In addition to the above information, The SCOOTER Store may also collect your zip code, credit/debit card number and expiration date, and other billing information when you order products through the Site. This information, in addition to other Active Information, may be used to process and fulfill your purchase orders.

##### Passive Information Collected

Our Site uses a standard feature of web browser software technology called "cookies" to "passively" collect information about how this site is used. Passive Information gathered may include the date and time of visits, browser information, the site pages viewed, time spent on this site, and the IP address of the computer accessing our site. IP addresses are collected for troubleshooting that may be necessary; for example, we may use the IP information to conduct research on questionable leads that have come through the Internet. Passive Information is collected on an aggregate basis without any continued association to your Active Information. If you do not wish to transmit "cookie" information about yourself, you may turn off the cookie function in your web browser (please consult the "Help" section of your browser to do so).

We use Passive Information to gather information about our Site's users for marketing campaigns and to enhance and design this Site to make it easier, faster and friendlier to use. Additionally, cookies help The SCOOTER Store know more information about how many people visit this Site, when they visit, and how they use this Site.

##### How Do We Secure Active and Passive Information?

We protect Active and Passive Information by using security measures, including encryption measures, designed to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure of, or accidental loss or destruction of, such Active and Passive Information. Unfortunately, however, no information is 100% secure when transmitted over the Internet. The SCOOTER Store is not responsible or liable for disclosure of your Active or Passive Information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access, or other causes beyond our reasonable control.

##### Do We Share Information?

We may provide aggregate Passive Information about Site traffic patterns and related Site information to our affiliates or reputable third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying data. Except as stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell or share your Active Information. We may share your Active Information with our affiliates and service providers to provide services and products you have requested.

We may also share your Active Information with carefully selected third-party vendors, who may use the Active Information shared to provide special opportunities and offers to you. Your Active Information will also be shared with to further process your application for products being sold to you by The SCOOTER Store.

In addition, we may disclose Passive Information, including aggregated data and statistics, in order to describe the Site to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. Additionally, we may disclose part or all of your Active Information when we believe, in good faith, that the law requires or compels such disclosure, or when we have good faith reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or property, the rights of another user or to prevent harm. Further, we may disclose information provided by you as part of any merger, sale, acquisition, or other acquisition of some or all of The SCOOTER Store or its assets.

##### How Can You Choose Not to Receive Information from Us or to Correct Your Information?

If you wish to delete or correct your information, please access our contact information at <http://www.thescooterstore.com/contactus/>. From this page, you may submit a Customer Care Request to correct or delete your information. You may also elect to be removed from our marketing lists by selecting [Remove me from the mailing list](http://www.thescooterstore.com/contactus/stopdirectmail.aspx), or be removed from our email lists by selecting [Unsubscribe from Email](http://www.thescooterstore.com/contactus/unsubscribe.aspx). Upon your specific request, we will remove your Active Information from all actively used files.

##### 3rd Party and Vendor Emails

In some instances another vendor or partner company will send an email on our behalf during the slight delay in getting you unsubscribed from the email messages. If you continue to receive email from us after you have unsubscribed from our [Unsubscribe from Email](http://www.thescooterstore.com/contactus/unsubscribe.aspx) page, please forward the email message to [emailhelp@thescooterstore.com](mailto:emailhelp@thescooterstore.com) and we will ensure you are removed from the list.

##### What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?

We are not responsible for the practices employed by sites linked to or from our Site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Site.

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our site to another site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other site, including sites which have a link on our site, is subject to that site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

##### What About Children's Privacy?

Protecting the privacy of children is very important to us. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personally-identifiable information from any person we know is a child under the age of 13. If we discover that we have received any information from a child under age 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately.

##### HIPAA - Notice of Privacy Practices

This notice describes how medical information about you may be used and disclosed and how you can get access to this information. Click here for more information.

We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy at our discretion. Please check back on this site as this Privacy Policy may be revised from time to time without notice to you.
